'당신 정말 아름답군!'
God, you're beautiful.
'우리가 왜 싸우는 거지?'
Why are we fighting this?
'당신도 나만큼이나
그렇게 되길 바라잖아'
You know you want it to happen
as much as I do.
'당신을 원해!
당신이 필요해!'
I want you. I need you.
'당신을 사랑하고 싶어'
Let me make love to you.
진실한 사랑에
토 달 생각은 없지만
I don't wanna stand in the way
of true love or anything..
멜론이라면 좀 덜 아플텐데
but I think a cantaloupe
might hurt less.
대사 연습하는 거야
No, I'm rehearsing my lines.
엄청 로맨틱한 장면이거든
They're giving me a romantic story
on Days of Our Lives.
처음이라 굉장히 떨려
잘 하고 싶은데 말야
It's the first time my character's gotten one.
I'm nervous. I want it to be good.
와, 너 이렇게 열심인거
처음 본다
I haven't seen you this worked-up since
you did that dog-food commercial..
진짜 말하는 개가 나오는줄
알았던 그 개밥광고 이후로 말야
and you thought you were gonna be
with a real talking dog.
그때 정말 실망이 컸지
Yeah, that was a disappointment.
녹화장에 와서 내 연기
어떤지좀 봐줄래?
You wanna come down to the set
and tell me if I'm doing okay?
정말이야?
- Are you serious?
- Yeah.
대신 지난번처럼
주책부리지 않는다고 약속해
You just have to promise not
to get thrown out again.
- 야! 그건 실수였어
- 그래?
- That was an honest mistake.
- Right.
"어머! 남자화장실이잖아?
저 참 바보 같죠?"
"Oh, my God. Is this the men's room?
I feel so foolish.
"어렸을 때부터
배우가 되고 싶었나요?"
Have you always known
you wanted to be an actor?"
그날 아주 짜릿했지
Yeah, that was an awesome day.
프렌즈 시즌 9
'꿈 속의 조이'
- 안녕
- 어서와
- Hey.
조만간 우리 식당에
와서 밥 먹지 않을래?
You guys wanna come eat dinner
at the restaurant in the next few weeks?
- 그래!
- 미안하지만 불가능해!
- I'd love to.
- Well, you can't.
- 앞으로 한달간 예약이 꽉 찼거든
- 나도 너희들 마사지 못해줘
- We're booked solid for the next month.
- Well, I can't give you a massage..
마사지사 면허가 또 취소됐거든
because my license
has been revoked again.
- 어쩌다가?
- 사고였어
- Phoebe, what happened?
- Well, it was an accident, you know.
오일이 많이 묻은 데다가
가끔은 손이 그냥 미끄러지거든
It's a lot of oil and sometimes
the hand just slips.
식당이 인기가 많은가 보지?
So the restaurant's doing well, you say?
정말 굉장해
내 요리를 먹으러 줄 선다니깐
It is so great. There are people
lining up in the street..
다음주 토요일엔
예약 대기자가 50명이야
to taste my food. Saturday,
there's a waiting list of 50 people.
나도 그 기분 알아
지난 학기에 두 학생이
I know how that feels.
Last semester, I had two students..
내가 가르치는 1시 수업을
듣고 싶어 했는데 학생수가 차서
who wanted to take my 1:00 class,
but it was full.
5시 수업을 들어야 했어
So they had to take my 5:00.
다른 느낌이겠다
That's not the same.
깜짝 선물을 준비했어!
빨리 짐싸!
Have I got a surprise for you.
Pack your bags.
너희 7년간은 이혼하지
않기로 했잖아!
Oh, no. You guys aren't supposed
to get divorced for seven years.
아냐, 모니카랑 버몬트에 있는
낭만적인 호텔에 갈거야
What? No, I'm taking Monica
to a romantic inn in Vermont.
와! 그래, 잘 생각했어
신혼 분위기 다시 내봐
Oh, good. Okay, good for you.
Trying to recapture the magic.
- 휴가 낼수 있어?
- 안그래도 요즘 식당 일이
- So can you get out of work?
- Honey, I can't.
- 바쁘단 얘길 하던 중이었어
- 휴가도 못낼 정도야?
- Things are crazy at the restaurant.
- You're really that busy?
미안해
도저히 안되겠어
Yeah. I'm sorry, I really am.
괜찮아
날짜를 바꿔볼게
That's okay. I'll just try and reschedule.
챈들러 빙이라고 합니다
Hi, this is Chandler Bing.
I made a reservation there..
예약 변경하려구요
and I need to change it.
변경이 안된다뇨?
다른 날짜에 가면 안될까요?
What do you mean, it's nonrefundable?
Well, can I just come some other time?
절대로 안된다구요?
Can't you make an exception?
내가 뉴욕의 커다란 식당
주방장이라고 얘기해!
Tell them I'm a chef
at a big New York restaurant.
그리고 난 2주후면 다시
마사지사가 될거라고 얘기해!
Tell them that in two weeks, I will once
again be a masseuse in good standing.
정말 억지로군요! 난 그 방값
지불할수 없습니다!
Look, this is ridiculous.
I'm not paying for that room, okay?
그래요! 고마워요!
Well, thank you very much.
버몬트에 가야겠는걸
Yeah, I'm going to Vermont.
걱정마, 여행보험으로
처리하면돼
- Don't worry, use your travel insurance.
- I don't have travel insurance.
난 여행보험 안들었어
이래서 미리미리
대비하고 살아야 한다니까
Well, this is what happens
when people live on the edge.
- 그래서 어떻게 할거야?
- 내가 갈게
- Honey, what are you gonna do?
- I'll go.
그럼 10시에 만나자
Okay, I'll pick you up at 10.
너랑 같이 가는거야?
Oh, go with you?
아.. 못가겠다
Oh, I can't go.
오빠랑 같이가지 그래?
Why don't you take Ross?
웃기지 않겠어? 남자 둘이
낭만적인 호텔에 가다니
Don't you think that'll be a little weird?
I mean, two guys in a romantic inn?
- 침대가 둘이면 상관없잖아
- 그건 그래
- No, not if the room has two beds.
- I guess.
그래도 좀..
"달빛 속의 보트유람"?
It still seems a little..
"Moonlight boat ride"?!
'실버컵 스튜디오'
조이, 올리비아가 순결을
잃은게 바로 이 침대니?
Joey, is this the bed
where Olivia lost her virginity?
몰라, 하지만 엑스트라 중
한명은 확실히 그랬지
I don't know,
but one of the extras sure did.
내 연기장면 보러 와줘서
정말 고맙다
Listen, Rach. Thanks again
for coming down to watch my scenes.
무슨 소리야? 네가 이런 일에
날 불러줬다는게..
Please, honey. Just the fact that you
want me here to support you, I'm..
어머! 크리스찬 선더스잖아?
진짜 멋있다!
Oh, my God. Is that Christian Saunders?
He is so gorgeous!
저 친구 게이야
And also, so gay.
내 상상 속에선 전혀
게이스럽지 않았는데..
Well, in my head,
he's done some pretty not-gay stuff.
크리스마스 파티때 산타클로스랑
아주 게이스럽게 놀았어
Well, at the Christmas party, him
and Santa did some definitely-gay stuff.
조이? 준비됐어요
Joey? Joey, we're ready for you.
알겠습니다
행운을 빌어줘
Okay. All right, wish me luck.
넌 잘 할테니까..
우와! 체이스 래시터잖아?!
Okay. Not that you need it, but good..
God! Is that Chase Lassiter?
- 저사람은 게이 아니지?
- 네가 여기 와서 배우들 게이인지
- He's straight, right?
- Rach, if you weren't here wondering..
아닌지 물어보지 않았다면 난 오늘
연기에 임할 용기가 안났을 거야
if these guys were gay,
I don't know if I could do this.
미안해, 조이!
행운을 빌어
I'm sorry, you're right.
I'm sorry. Good luck.
시작할까요?
조용히 하세요!
On a bell, please. Quietly.
액션!
And action!
드레이크!
여긴 웬일이죠?
Drake, what are you doing here?
그남자와 결혼하는건 실수야!
Stopping you from marrying
the wrong man..
그걸 막으러 왔어!
and making the biggest
mistake of your life.
- 나가요
- 그사람 사랑하지 않잖아!
- Get out.
- You don't love him.
당신이 사랑에 대해 뭘 알아요?
What do you know about love?
다리 밑에서 당신과 키스했던
그날밤의 감정은 잘알고 있어!
I know what I felt that night
when we kissed under the bridge.
- 그일은 없었던 걸로 해요
- 그럼 이건?
- That kiss never happened.
- Well, what about this one?
어서 나가요!
Now, I told you to get out.
좋아! 가겠어!
Fine, I'll go.
한가지만 물어볼게
But let me ask you one question.
낯이 많이 익군요
우리 어디선가..?
- You look real familiar. Have we..?
- Shh! He's asking her a question.
쉿! 물어볼게 있다잖아요!
남은 평생 우리 관계에 대해
아무 미련없이 살 자신 있어?
Can you live the rest of your life never
knowing what we could have been?
- 선택의 여지가 없어요
- 아니
- I don't have a choice.
- Yes, you do.
당신에겐 선택권이 있어
선택의 여지가 없는 사람은 나야
Yes, you do. I'm the one who doesn't
have a choice because I..
왜냐하면 난 당신을
사랑하지 않을수 없으니까
Because I can't stop loving you.
- 그런말 하지 말아요
- 그만 하라고 해줘
- Don't say that.
- Tell me to stop.
당신을..
Just..
사랑하지 말라고..
tell me to stop.
- 컷!
- 안돼!
- Cut!
- No!
마음대로 하세요
그게 감독님 일이니까
Or, cut. You know, that's your call.
- 다 맛있었어요
- 고맙습니다
- Everything was delicious.
- Thank you.
특히 오리가 아주 훌륭했어요
It was. The duck in particular
was superb.
고맙습니다
Thank you.
아무 말씀도 안하시네요?
You haven't said anything.
사실 불만이 좀 있습니다
Actually, I do have one small complaint.
말씀하세요
비평은 언제나 환영이에요
Well, please, I welcome criticism.
식당 밖에서 노래하는 가수
때문에 분위기가 깨져요
The musician right outside the restaurant
is kind of a mood killer.
무슨 가수요?
What musician?
아르헨티나라는 나라
한번도 가본적 없지만
50페소면 사람 비장을
살수 있지
사람 비장을
살수 있지, 올레!
여기서 뭐하는 거야?
What are you doing here?
식당에 손님들이 줄 선다기에
노래 불러주러 왔지
You said you had customers lined up
in the street, so I'm here to entertain.
- 그거 좋지
- 정말 기분 좋아
- Great.
- Yeah, it really has been great too.
전에 내 노래 들어본 사람들인지
They must have seen me
play before..
내 노래를 신청하는거 있지?
because they requested
a bunch of my songs.
"집어치워!"
Yeah, "You Suck"..
"입 닥치고 집에 가!"
그런 노래들 말야
and "Shut Up and Go Home."
있잖니, 피비? 내가 네 음악을
얼마나 좋아하는지 알지?
Listen, Phoebe. You know how much
I love listening to your music..
- 그런데..
- 그런데 뭐?
- but..
- But what?
여긴 품격이 있는 곳이거든
This is kind of a classy place.
아! 무슨 말인지 알겠어
Okay, say no more.
그녀가 뚱보라서가 아녜요
그녀에게선 쓰레기 냄새가 나!
다함께!
Everyone!
그녀가 뚱보라서가 아녜요
그녀에게선 쓰레기 냄새가 나!
이젠 격에 맞지?
Classy, huh?
챈들러 빙입니다
예약했는데요
Hi, Chandler Bing. I have a reservation.
체스트넛 인에 잘 오셨습니다
어디서 오셨죠?
Welcome to the Chestnut lnn.
Where are you joining us from?
- 뉴욕이요
- 빅 애플!
- New York.
- The Big Apple.
이 친구가 좀 흥분했어요
He's wound up. We had to stop at every
maple-candy stand on the way here.
오는길에 메이플 사탕
파는 데마다 들렀거든요
선물 주려고 산 사탕
내가 다 먹었어요!
I ate all my gifts for everybody.
죄송합니다만 선생님의
예약기록이 없는데요
I'm sorry, there's no record
of your reservation in the computer.
그럴리가 없어요
다시 한번 봐주겠어요?
- That's impossible. Check again, please.
- Check again, please.
다시 봐주세요
- 죄송합니다, 없는데요
- 없대
- I'm sorry, it's not here.
- It's not there.
그게 무슨 소리죠?
어제 예약 취소하려고 전화했더니
Let me get this straight. I called
to try to cancel my reservation..
불가능하다고 하더군요
그래서 차 몰고 6시간을 달려왔는데
was told it's not refundable. Then we
drove six hours all the way up here..
- 예약이 안되어 있다고요?
- 저도 어쩔수가 없네요
- and now we don't have a reservation?
- I don't know what to say.
자기도 어쩔수 없대
She doesn't know what to say.
제일 싼 방으로 줘요
Just give us
the cheapest room you have.
지금 남은 방은 600달러짜리
디럭스 스위트뿐입니다
The only thing we have available
is our deluxe suite. The rate is $600.
- 이런법이 어디 있습니까!
- 이런법이 어디 있어!
- That's insane.
- It's totally insane.
돌아가자! 가는 길에
사탕 가게마다 전부 들르자
Dude, let's drive home. We'll hit all the
maple-candy stores on the way back..
문 닫았으면 단풍나무 수액
짜서 사탕을 직접 만들자!
and if they're closed, then maybe we'll
tap a tree and make some ourselves.
그방에 이친구 가둬 둘 만한
옷장 있어요?
Does that room have a closet
I can lock him in?
- 그방 주세요
- 알겠습니다
- We'll take it.
- Great.
이건 순 날강도 아냐?!
300달러씩 내야 한다니?
They are totally ripping us off!
Three hundred dollars each?
"300달러씩"?
난 네 데이트잖아
"Each?" I'm your date.
그럼 돈은 돈대로 내고
재미는 못보는 거군
So I pay for everything
and have no sex.
모니카 전의 내 삶이여!
Oh, life before Monica.
걱정마
Dude, don't worry about it.
네 돈 되찾을 방법을 알고 있어
여긴 고급호텔이라
I know how to make your money back.
This is a nice hotel. Plenty of amenities.
제공되는 물품이 많을거야! 몽땅
쓸어가자구, 저 사과만 해도 그래
We just load up on those.
Like those apples. Instead of taking one..
난 6개 가져갈래
I take six.
그래, 사과 하나에 100달러면
계산이 딱 맞네
Great. At $100 an apple, we're there.
내말 무슨 뜻인지 알잖아
금방 본전 챙길수 있어
Come on, you get the idea. You know,
we'll make our money back in no time.
- 너 떨고 있잖아!
- 당분 때문인가봐
- Dude, you're shaking.
- It's the sugar. Could you hold the apple?
사과좀 들어줄래?
- 안녕
- 어서와
- Hi.
- Hey.
하루종일 네가 한 연기
생각해봤는데
Joey, I gotta tell you, I have been
thinking all day about that scene you did.
너 정말 굉장했어!
I mean, you were amazing.
작품이 좋았지, 뭐
감독도 좋았고
You know, the writing was good.
And the director's good.
- 동료 배우들도 잘했지
- 그래
And my costar's good.
하지만 나만큼 잘하진 못했어!
But they're not as good as me!
내일은 어떻게 되는지
얘기해줘
You have to tell me
what happens tomorrow.
나도 지금 막 대본 받았어
대사 연습 도와줄래?
I'm going over the script now.
Wanna read lines with me?
내가?
난 연기자도 아닌걸
Me? Oh, I'm not an actress.
- 그럼 모니카한테 부탁해야지
- 안돼! 내가 할래!
- All right, I can ask Monica.
- Screw her! That part is mine!
좋아
이 페이지 맨 처음부터 읽어
Okay, so just from the top
of the page right here.
알았어
Okay.
안녕, 드레이크
여기 나타나다니 놀랍네요
Hello, Drake.
I'm surprised to see you here.
- 어떻게 그자랑 결혼할수 있지?
- 그럼 나더러 어쩌라구요?
- I can't believe you married him.
- Well, what choice did I have?
그는 내 여동생을 지하 감옥에
감금해 두고 있어요!
He was keeping my sister in a dungeon.
우리는 어떡하구? 우리가 느낀
그 모든 감정들은 어떡하지?
So, what about us?
Everything we feel for each other?
다 끝났어요
인정해야만 해요
It's over. You have to accept that.
난 그렇게 못해!
다시는 당신을 안을수 없고
How can I, knowing I'll never
hold you in my arms again..
당신을 만질수도 없고
당신 입술을 느낄수도 없어!
or touch your skin or feel your lips..
다시는 당신을
사랑할수 없다구!
knowing I'll never make love to you?
다시는 당신에게
키스할수 없다는걸
How can I accept
that I can never kiss you again..
어떻게 인정하란 거지?
when it's all I can do
not to kiss you right now?
키스해줘
Kiss me.
뭐?
What?
키스해줘
Kiss me.
- 레이첼, 그런 대사는 없어
- 내가 하는 말이야
- Rach, it doesn't say that.
- No, I'm saying it.
- 하지만
- 어서.. 아무 말도 하지마
- But..
- Just don't talk.
이건 새로운 꿈이네
Well, that's new.
여기 206호인데요
Hi, this is Ross Geller in suite 206.
필요한 물건 몇 가지를
I've forgotten a couple of things.
안가져왔는데 보내주겠어요?
Could you have some complimentary
toiletries sent up to my room?
칫솔, 치약..
Thank you.
Okay, a toothbrush, toothpaste..
면도기, 구강청정제, 탈취제,
치실, 1회용 밴드, 면도크림..
razor, mouthwash, deodorant, floss,
Band-Aids, shaving cream, after-shave.
더 있는데 생각이 안나네요
And I feel like I'm forgetting something.
내가 말한것 말고
구비된 물건이 또 뭐가 있죠?
Is there anything else you have
that I haven't asked for already?
좋아요
탐폰도 올려 보내주세요
Yeah, go ahead,
send up some tampons.
- 뭐 가져왔어?
- 신문
- What'd you get?
- USA Today.
잘했어
다른 신문이랑 같이 둬
Nice. Put it with the others.
사과도 두개 더 가져왔지!
And I also got two more apples.
네개만 더 있으면
한상자 되겠다!
We're four short of a bushel!
진짜 살맛난다!
이동네 정말 마음에 들어!
God, I feel so alive.
I love being in the country!
식당에서 근사한 소금통이랑
Also, got these great
salt and pepper shakers..
- 후추통도 집어왔지
- 오, 그건 도가 지나쳐
- from the restaurant.
- That's not cool.
다른건 도가
지나치지 않구?!
Dude, none of this is cool.
도둑질과
우리의 권리를 찾는 것은
Look, Chandler, you have to find
the line between stealing..
분명히 구별해야 해
and taking what the hotel owes you.
예를 들어볼게
헤어 드라이어? 안돼
For example: A hair dryer, no, no.
샴푸와 린스?
그건 괜찮지
But shampoos and conditioners,
yes, yes.
다시 말해 소금통은
도를 넘는거란 말야
Now, the salt shaker is off limits.
하지만 소금은..
But the salt..
생각좀 하고 행동할걸
I wish I'd thought this through.
무슨 뜻인지 알았어
이 전등은.. 호텔 재산이지
I think I get what you mean, though.
Like, the lamp is the hotel's..
하지만 전구는..
벌써 뺐구나!
but the bulbs..
Oh, you already got that.
내가 호텔 한두번 와봤냐?
Not my first time in a hotel, my friend.
- 그럼 이건 어때?
- 안돼, 안돼
- Okay, how about this?
- No, no, no.
- 리모콘은 안돼
- 알아, 하지만 건전지는?
- You can't take the remote control.
- Yes, but the batteries.
감사합니다!
Thank you. Thank you very much.
- 우리 메이플 사탕으로 자축하자!
- 안돼!
- Let's celebrate with some maple candy.
- No!
어디 숨겼는지만이라도
가르쳐줘!
At least tell me where you hid it.
- 뭐하나 물어봐도 돼?
- 그래
- Can I ask you a question?
- Yeah.
낭만적이면서..
Have you ever had any..
이상한 꿈꾼적 있어?
weird, romantic dreams?
글쎄
Let me think.
어렸을때 맥치즈 시장과
결혼하는 꿈을 꾼적 있어
When I was younger, I used to dream
that I got married to Mayor McCheese.
첫날밤에 내가 그사람
머리를 먹는 꿈이었지
And on our wedding night,
I ate his head.
알았어
Okay.
내꿈은 그런 것과는
Well, this is like that..
전혀 달라
in no way.
어젯밤 꿈속에서
조이와 키스하고 싶었어
I had a dream last night
that I wanted to kiss Joey.
와! 진짜 제대로된 키스 말야?
Wow! You mean like
"kiss him" kiss him?
그래!
아주 강렬했어
Oh, yeah.
I mean, it was pretty intense.
- 왜 그런 꿈을 꾼거야?
- 몰라
- What brought that on?
- I don't know.
어제 조이가 러브신
연기하는걸 봐서 그런걸까?
Maybe it had to do with the fact
I saw him do a love scene.
- 러브신? 누구랑?
- 올리비아?
- A love scene? With who?
- Olivia.
올리비아?!
코너랑 결혼했잖아?!
Olivia?! I thought she was
marrying Connor?!
아, 그래
현실이 더 중요하지
Oh, right. Real life more important.
- 그꿈이 뭘 의미하는것 같아?
- 글쎄
- You think my dream means anything?
- I don't know.
어제 러브신
연기하는걸 봤다며
I mean, you saw him do a love scene.
조이한테 끌린다기보다
드레이크한테 끌린거 아닐까?
So maybe you don't have a thing for Joey.
Maybe you have a thing for Drake.
꿈에서 조이가 드레이크의
대사를 읽고 있었어
Well, it was Joey reading
Drake's lines in the dream.
그럴줄 알았지
심리학이라면
Of course it was. Trust me,
when it comes to psychology..
내가 꿰고 있으니까 내말 믿어
I know what I'm talking about.
대학때 심리학
두과목이나 수강했다구
I took two psych classes in college.
같은 과목 두번 들었잖아!
You took the same class twice.
- 어려웠단 말야!
- 알아
- It was hard!
- I know.
- 안녕
- Hey.
- Hi, Phoebe.
자, 모니카, 너희 식당에서
연주할때 입으려고 준비한 거야
Here, Monica, look what I got to wear
when I play at your restaurant.
기다려봐
Wait.
"포경 수술 안한 남자의 발라드"가
훨씬 품위있게 들릴거야
Right? I think this might even class up
"The Ballad of the Uncircumcised Man."
- 어, 피비?
- 응?
Phoebe..
내가 얘길 제대로
안한것 같은데
maybe I wasn't clear before.
여기서 네 음악 듣는건 좋지만
I really love listening
to your music here.
우리 식당은 고급식당이야
But my restaurant,
it's sort of an upscale place.
알았어, 집사한테 금고에서
다이아몬드 꺼내오라고 할게
Right, yeah, okay. I'll ask the butler
to fetch my diamonds out of the vault.
피비, 네 옷 때문이 아냐
Phoebe, it's not what you wear.
네 노래 때문이야
It's sort of your songs.
앞으로 우리 식당에서
노래하지 않았으면 좋겠어
I just don't think you should play
at the restaurant anymore.
그래, 알았어
Okay. Fine, I'll just..
모자 돌려줘야겠다
I'll take the hat back.
됐어
There.
회사에서 아주 웃기는
일이 있었는데..
Hey, so, you guys, the funniest
thing happened at work the..
내 노래가 너희 식당 수준에
안맞는다는 거야?
My songs aren't good enough
for your restaurant?
아직 안끝났구나
Okay, we're still on that.
네 노래가 수준이
안맞는다고는 안했어!
- I didn't say they weren't good enough.
- Then what's wrong with them?
그럼 대체 뭐가 문제야?
눈곱만큼도 안되는 네 잘난
요리랑 안어울린다는 거야?
What, they don't go with your
tiny portions of pretentious food?
- 눈곱만큼?
- "전채로"
- Tiny portions?
- Yeah, well, "Excuse me.
"훈제연어를 시켰는데요
어디있죠? 안 보여요!"
I ordered the smoked salmon appetizer,
but I can't see it. I can't see it."
- 중요한건 양이 아냐!
- 질도 중요하지 않은것 같던데?
- Phoebe, it's not about quantity.
- Well, it's not about quality.
그래? 질에 대해 얘기해볼까?
Oh, really?
You wanna talk about quality?
혹시 '선율'이란 말 들어봤니?
Have you ever heard of a "key"?
It's what some people sing in.
어떤 음악가들은
선율을 중요하게 생각하더라!
난 적어도 모든 노래마다
마늘냄새 풍기진 않아!
Well, at least all my songs
don't taste like garlic.
세상엔 다른 양념도
많이 있단다, 모니카!
Yeah, there are other
ingredients, Monica.
좋아, 그렇게 나온다 이거지?
So that's what we're doing.
그거 알아? 카페에서
네 노래 들을 때마다
When I'm in a coffeehouse bopping
along to one of your songs..
나 귀마개 해!
I'm wearing earplugs.
귀마개? 마늘이 아니구?
Earplugs or cloves of garlic?
좋아! 아까 내가 한말 취소야!
You know what?
I take back what I said before.
계속 노래해! 네 노래 듣기 싫어서
사람들이 식당으로 들어올 거야!
Keep playing at the restaurant, because
with your music driving people inside..
덕분에 우리 식당 바 매상
팍팍 오를걸!
my bar sales
have gone up like crazy.
그사람들 뭘 마실거래?
마늘 마티니?
What are people having,
the garlic martini?
그래서 회사에서 일어난 일
얘기해줄까?
So you wanna hear my work story?
나중에 해줄게
I'll save it.
계산서입니다
머무는 동안 즐거우셨나요?
Here's your bill.
We hope you enjoyed your stay.
그럼요, 전등은 모두
그대로 뒀습니다
Oh, we did.
And you still have all your lamps.
- 이런, 세금은 생각 못했는걸
- 걱정마
- I didn't factor in the room tax.
- Dude, don't worry about it.
내가 청소아줌마 수레를 발견했어
우리가 챙긴게 훨씬 많아
I found an unattended maid's cart.
We're way ahead of the game.
- 이럴수가!
- 왜?
- Oh, my God.
- What?
그릇에 새로운게 담겨있어!
There's something new in the bowl.
- 많이 챙겼잖아, 그냥가자
- 싫어! 나 솔방울 가져갈래
- Look, we have enough. Just walk away.
- No, but I want the pine cones.
- 밖에도 온통 숲이야
- 그거랑은 달라!
- There's a forest right outside.
- It's not the same.
- 안돼, 저 여자가 볼거야
- 안잡히고 잘할수 있어
- No, look. She's gonna see us.
- No, she won't. I'm sly.
알았어! 빨리 집어와!
Okay, go quick.
그동안 즐거웠습니다
Thank you for a delightful stay.
와! 메이플 사탕이다!
My maple candy!
자부 식당의 음식은
먹으면 죽어요
너였구나! 난 누가 고양이가 든
가방을 매달아 놓은줄 알았지!
It's just you. I thought someone was
swinging a bag of cats against the wall.
빨리 들어가봐, 그래야 요리마다
마늘이 무더기로 들어가지
You'd better get back in that kitchen.
The garlic's not gonna overuse itself.
- 노래 그만해!
- 왜?
- Okay, you have to stop playing now.
- Why?
내 음악 싫어하는 사람은
너뿐인걸?
The only person my playing
is bothering is you.
- 그래? 좋아, 끝장을 보자구
- 마늘까는 손 저리 치워!
- Oh, yeah? Let's settle this. Come on.
- Get your garlic peelers off me.
여러분, 잠깐만요!
Excuse me? Excuse me?
이곳의 주방장
모니카 겔러입니다
Hi, I'm Monica Geller.
I'm the head chef here.
조금은 박수가
나올줄 알았는데..
Okay, I was actually expecting
a little applause there, but whatever.
간단한 질문 하나 할게요
Quick question.
By a show of hands..
밖에서 이 아가씨가 부르는
노래가 거슬리는 분?
how many of you were bothered
by this woman's singing outside?
알았어요, 그럼
저도 한가지 물어보죠
Okay, okay. Well, I have a question.
손 내리셔도 돼요
You can put your hand down.
좀전에 제 기타 케이스에
침 뱉은걸로 충분해요
You made your point earlier
when you spit in my guitar case.
좋아요, 제 노래
마음에 드셨던 분들?
Okay, okay. How many of you
enjoyed the music outside?
좋아요, 그럼 또 물어보죠
음악은 좋지만 식당 분위기와
Let me ask you this question.
How many thought the music was fine..
안맞는다고 생각하는 분?
but not in keeping with the tone
of the restaurant?
이 식당 분위기가 잘난 척하고
마늘냄새 난다고 생각하는 분?
Okay, well, who identified this restaurant's
tone as "pretentious-comma-garlicky"?
음식이 맛이 있고, 멋을 부리긴
해도 불만없다고 생각하는 분?
Okay, who thinks the food is delicious
and a little pretension never hurt anyone?
음식도 좋고 음악도 좋은데
Okay, well, all right, who thinks
the food is fine, the music was fine..
지금 이 투표에 기분 잡치신 분?
but your evening was ruined
by this incessant poll-taking?
죄송합니다
Excuse us.
질문이 하나 더 있어
All right, here's a question.
자기 식당 챙기느라 친구 노래에
Who was so worried about
her restaurant being fancy..
너무 민감하게 반응해서
that she made a big deal about
her friend playing her music..
지금 엄청 반성하고 있는 사람?
and feels really bad about it now?
어리석은 고집으로 친구의
Well, who was so stupid
and stubborn..
요리를 심하게 비난했지만
that she lashed out
against her friend's cooking..
실제로는 친구의 솜씨를
굉장하다고 생각하는 사람?
which she actually thinks
is pretty great?
- 미안해
- 나도 미안해
- I'm sorry.
- I'm sorry too.
잠깐만 기다릴래?
금방 저녁식사 준비해줄게
Hey, you wanna stick around
and I'll whip you up some dinner?
공짜라면 좋아!
Yeah, as long as it's free.
여기 음식값
터무니없이 비싸서..
The food here is ridiculously overpr..
모니카가 나 손드는거 계속
귀엽게 봐주길 바라는 사람?
Who hopes the hand-raising thing is still
cute enough that you won't hate me?
- 안녕?
- 어서와
- Hey.
조이, 너 뒤통수에
땅콩버터 묻었어
Joey, do you have peanut butter
on the back of your head?
다 닦은줄 알았는데
Oh, man. I thought I got it all.
어떻게
How..?
된거야?
How?
땅콩버터 음료 만들었거든
I was making a peanut butter
smoothie, right?
믹서 맨위에 끼우는 이 작은
플라스틱을 못 찾겠더라구
I couldn't find this little plastic thingy
that goes in the top of the blender.
그거 없다고 대수겠냐 싶었지
And I thought, "Well, you know,
how important can that be?" Right?
그런데 없으면 안되는 거더라
Turns out, very.
역시 드레이크만 좋았어
Wow, definitely just Drake.
- 뭐라구?
- 드레이크는 어떻게 됐어?
- What?
- How's it going with Drake?
- 잘 안될것 같아
- 뭐?
- I don't think it's going very well.
- What?
어제 장면 정말 멋있었어!
That scene I saw was so good.
내일 찍을 장면 생각하면
불안해 죽겠어
Well, I'm feeling really insecure
about the one we're shooting tomorrow.
그거 내가 격려해주길
바라고 해보는 소리니?
Is this that thing you do when you say
you're bad so I'll give you a compliment?
그런면도 있지
A little.
하지만 진짜 걱정이야
No, I really am worried. I have to make it
convincing that I'm in love with Olivia.
올리비아에 대한 사랑을
설득력 있게 보여줘야 하거든
- 그런데?
- 그런 연기는 해본적이 없어
- So?
- So I've never played that.
어려울것 없어
너도 사랑에 빠져본적 있잖아
Oh, honey, it can't be that hard.
I mean, you've been in love before.
그래, 딱 한번
Well, just once..
너한테 말야
with you.
이거좀 어색하네
Okay. Well, this could be
a little awkward.
빨리 넘기는게 좋겠다
I'm just gonna blow past it.
실제 생활의 경험을 살려서
Well, look, can't you just use
that method-actor thing..
연기하는 메소드 연기를 해봐
where you use your real-life memories
to help you in your performance?
알아듣게 얘기해봐
What the hell are you talking about?
네가 사랑에 빠졌을때
어떤 느낌이었는지 잘 생각해봐
All right, look, just try to remember
how you felt when you were in love..
그리고 그 감정을
연기하면서 살려보는 거야
and think about that
when you're playing the scene.
아, 알았어
할수 있을것 같아
Okay. Yeah, I think I can do that.
내일 파티 장면이 있거든?
Yeah. Okay, there's this
party scene coming up.
올리비아를 껴안고
And Olivia and her husband are there..
키스하고 싶지만
드레이크는 그럴수가 없어
and all Drake wants to do is
grab her and kiss her, but he can't.
생각해보니까 그때 나도
널 안고 키스하고 싶었지만
That makes me think about those times
I wanted to grab you and kiss you..
아무것도 모르는 너한테
내색할수 없어서
but you didn't know, so I would
just pretend everything was cool..
정말 괴로웠어
but really it was killing me.
그런 얘기 한번도 안했잖아
Joey, you never
talked about that before.
참, 또 있어!
Hey, you know what else I could use?
드레이크가 올리비아 침실에
몰래 들어가는 장면이 있거든?
There's this scene where Drake
sneaks into Olivia's bedroom..
물론 우리 사이엔
그런일은 없었지
and she doesn't know he's there,
which never happened with us.
안된다는걸 알지만
그녀가 너무 보고 싶었던 거야
I mean, he knows he shouldn't be there,
but he just wants to look at her.
그리고
You know?
이런 기억도 있어
아침에 화장기 없는 널보며
And I remember all those mornings
before you even put on your makeup..
정말 예쁘다고 생각했는데..
when I would think to myself,
"My God, she is beautiful."
너한테 말할수가 없어서
너무 가슴 아팠어
And it hurt so much because
I knew I could never tell you.
하지만 널 볼수 있다는
것만으로도 난 좋았어
But it was worth it just to be there
looking at you.
고마워!
정말 큰 도움이 됐어!
Thanks, dude. This is great!
버몬트에서 가져온 선물이야
I got you something from Vermont.
탐폰과 소금 말고 또 있어?
Besides tampons and salt?
와!
Oh, my God.
메이플 사탕이네!
정말 고마워
Maple candy. That's so sweet of you.
텅 비었잖아?
That's weird, it's empty.
안녕, 얘들아
무슨 일이야? 나하고 놀래?
Hi, you guys. What's going on?
You guys wanna hang out or..?
'윙'하는 소리 안들리니?
Do you guys hear a buzzing?